Hey everyone. We've all seen the 'AI is changing the world' videos.
But most of it feels like noise.
Today, I want to pull back the curtain and show you exactly how I built a high-end brand—
RiseOra—from nothing but an idea to a full strategy, visual identity, and content engine.
And I did it using AI. Not to cut corners, but to amplify the vision.
If you’ve been sitting on an idea because you didn’t think you had the 'skills,' this video is for you.
I’m your big brother in this process. Let’s get into it.
It starts with the soul.
I used AI to help me articulate what was in my head.
I fed it my mission: To empower individuals to rise into their highest identity.
But the AI helped me refine the pillars. We came up with the 'RISE' method.
Key Takeaway: Don't just ask AI for 'a brand.' Tell it YOUR values first.
Then ask it to architect a system around them.
Next: The look.
I wanted 'Minimalist, High-end, Bronze and Sage.'
I used image generators to iterate on logos.
I didn't take the first thing it gave me. I poked it. I prodded it.
I refined the prompts until it felt like RiseOra.
Big Brother Moment: Precision beats volume. Take the time to get the aesthetic right.
It’s the first thing people feel.
The biggest hurdle is consistency. I used AI to draft the first 30 days of content.
But here’s the secret: I edited every single word.
AI gives you the skeleton; you give it the heart.
I’ll show you the scripts we generated for the flagship channel and how I’m using tools like HeyGen and Runway to animate them.
People ask me why I’m sharing the 'secret sauce.' It’s because the technology is just a tool.
The vision is yours. RiseOra is about rising inward first.
You can’t build a higher-level brand if you’re operating at a lower-level mindset.
That’s why this channel exists. To bridge that gap.
If this helped you, download the 'RiseOra Morning Protocol' I built—link is in the description.
It’s the same discipline I used to get this project off the ground.
Rise inward. Rise upward. I’ll see you in the next one.